pacsun.com 2017-10-15

# PacSun's Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

(Last updated February 4, 2016)

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THE PACSUN SERVICES.

## OVERVIEW

We value our relationship with you and your privacy is important to us. Below we describe information that we may receive for in connection with your use of the PacSun Services (as defined in our [Terms of Use](http://www.pacsun.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-pacsun-Site/default/Page-Show?cid=terms-and-conditions)), how and why we receive it, your options, and the efforts we make to safeguard it all.

By using the PacSun Services, you are consenting to the manner in which PacSun will receive, use, disclose and otherwise manage your information, as set forth below in this Privacy Policy. Additionally, when you provide information to PacSun, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current, and complete information.

## WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This Privacy Policy covers PacSun's treatment of certain information obtained or disclosed by PacSun, including information we receive when you use the PacSun Services or share information with any of PacSun's third party partners. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with this policy and [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus) if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that PacSun does not own or control, or to individuals whom PacSun does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties from which PacSun may obtain or to which PacSun may disclose user information as set forth in this Policy. The practices of such third parties are governed by their respective applicable privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

## POLICY CHANGES

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy or our information practices change in the future, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on the Site and/or the App. Your continued use of the Services following any changes to this policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

## INFORMATION WE RECEIVE ABOUT YOU

We receive information about you when you visit and/or use our Services, including certain personal information about you and certain non-personal information about you. In some cases, we may request that you provide some of the information identified below in order to obtain access certain services that we provide. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to access these Services. Our affiliates or certain other third parties also receive certain information about you when you when you use or access the PacSun Services, including the information described below.

We receive certain information about you when you visit and/or use our Services, including personal information, which is information that can be used to personally identify you. This information may be obtained directly by PacSun or through any of its third party partners, and includes but is not limited to your first name, last name, birthdate, gender, billing address(es), shipping address(es), e-mail address(es), telephone number(s), payment information (including but not limited to credit card, debit card, gift card, rewards program, or coupon code information), location information (including but not limited to continent, providers, country, region, zip code, city, store vicinity, and others), order and purchase history, search queries, product and service preferences, account preferences, status, and information (including but not limited to username(s), password(s), and settings, and others), contact lists, and others.

We also automatically collect certain non-personal information about your visit to the PacSun Services, including the device(s) you use to access our Services. Non-personal information is data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with you, and includes but is not limited to technical information about how you access the Services, including but not limited to browser information, operating system, device information, unique device identifiers, IP address, referring site/application, App version, visit metrics, action metrics, page view metrics, search metrics, and others.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, aggregated and anonymized personal information is considered non-personal information. If we do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for so long as it remains combined.

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE RECEIVE ABOUT YOU

We use and store the information that we receive about you, including your personal information, to necessary to conduct our business and to provide you and other users with the best possible products and services. As some examples, we use and store your information to fulfill orders, to provide you with suggestions and information in which you may be interested (including but not limited to offers related to your purchases through the Services and/or in-store), to measure or understand effectiveness of advertisements you and others see (including but not limited to serving you targeted advertisements), to protect the integrity and operation the Services, and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement.

To conduct our business and to best serve you, we may share or provide access to your information, including your personal information, with certain third parties, including but not limited to service providers that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have received your permission, given you notice (such as telling you about it in this Privacy Policy, or removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it.

We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including but not limited to providing it to third parties for marketing, advertising, analytics, or other uses.

We may also, in certain instances, disclose your information, including your personal information, when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, or bring legal action to protect your safety or rights or the safety or rights of PacSun or others. We may also disclose your information, including your personal information, when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required by law or as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

If PacSun is sold to or merges with another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets, subject only to agreement by the acquirer that the information will be subject to the same or substantially similar privacy protections as those established by this Privacy Policy, and without any requirement of a consumer privacy ombudsman. This may include personal information.

We store your information for as long as is necessary to conduct our business and to provide the best possible products and services to you, including for the uses described above.

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

Protecting your information is important to us. We use industry standard technology to protect the security of your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us. You agree that PacSun and our affiliates will have no liability for disclosure of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

## MAKING PURCHASES

When you place an order with PacSun, we ask you to provide Payment Method, Credit Card Account Number and Expiration Date (if applicable), Name (as it appears on credit card), "Bill To" Address (as it appears on your credit card statement), "Ship To" Address (if different from billing address), Daytime Phone Number, Email Address.

This information is necessary to process your order, and we assure you that your information, including your personal information, is transmitted over the most secure servers available. By making a purchase via the Services, you consent to our providing your information, including your personal information, to third parties as is necessary to process the requested transaction, including but not limited to third parties included credit card processors and banks. We further guarantee you will only pay for authorized items that you have ordered.

You will have the option of saving certain information, including your personal information, in our system for your convenience with respect to future purchases. The information is stored in the form of a "cookie" in your computer. Even though you need cookies to be enabled to make an online purchase, it is not necessary to save information via cookies if you choose not to.

PacSun collaborates with government agencies and security organizations to prevent fraud and fraudulent use of your information, including your personal information. During fraud prevention investigations, we may share information, including your personal information, with the agencies that assist us, as permitted and required by US law. Usage is strictly assigned to assist and prevent fraud investigations.

By registering an account with PacSun, your checkout will be quicker and more efficient, with easy access to your order history, shipping preferences, wish lists, and special offers. If you're not comfortable shopping online and wish to phone in your order, you are welcome to do so.

## ELECTRONIC AND CATALOG SUBSCRIPTIONS

If you sign up for our electronic and catalog subscriptions, you'll be the first to hear about up-coming sales, online exclusive discounts, contests and more. For example, you can sign up to receive our PacSun email newsletter, outlet emails, and our seasonal catalog during check-out and in various locations of the Services.

You'll always be able to unsubscribe from these electronic and catalog subscriptions, and we have a Contact Preference Center where you can manage these subscriptions so you only get what you're interested in. For more information, please visit your Contact Preference Center or [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus).

## ONLINE CONTESTS AND SWEEPSTAKES

We're always throwing down new, fun online contests and sweepstakes at PacSun. Enter, you could win!

Most sweepstakes and contests are open to U.S. residents 13 years and older. If you are under the age of majority in your state, make sure you get your parent's permission before entering any personal info.

To enter a given sweepstakes or contest, you may need to provide certain information to us, including personal information. If you are one of our winners, we'll use this information to contact you. Contest sponsors may utilize your info based on which opt-in(s) you have selected on the sweepstakes or contest entry pages.

## COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

Cookies are data files saved to your computer's hard drive when you visit a site. A "session cookie" expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A "persistent cookie" stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date, the cookie information is still available.

We use session and persistent cookies, either directly or through a third party partner, as well as along other tracking technologies (including but not limited to pixel tags and web beacons) to collect information about you in order to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible services and products. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests.

We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

## DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

PacSun relies on third-party vendors and service providers to provide support and assistance for our Services and products. We may share your personal information with such third parties in order to help us conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products and services. We may contract with various third-party service providers in furtherance of this goal, including but not limited to payment processors, website hosting partners, banks, cookie providers, and others. We also work with third party advertising, marketing and analytics partners to serve ads on this or other sites, using information collected through the use of industry standard technologies such as cookies and pixel tags. These third parties may receive information about you over time and across different websites when you use or visit the PacSun Services.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with third parties unless we have received your permission, given you notice (such as telling you about it in this Privacy Policy, or removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it. Where we share your personal information with service providers or any other third parties who perform services on our behalf, except as otherwise provided herein, they will be contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible products and services.

We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose, including providing it to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## CHILDREN

The Services are not directed to persons under age 13. Users must be at least 13 years of age to access, use, or register for the Services. We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from persons under age 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a user under the age of 13, without first receiving verifiable parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

If you are a parent and you think we have inadvertently collected personal information from your child who is under 13, you may [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus) to request that we delete his or her information from our records.

If you are a child who is under 18, and would like more information on how you can delete comments or other content that you have posted on the Services, you may [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus) to request instructions on how to delete this content from the Services.

## DO NOT TRACK

Because we use your information that we collect to conduct our business, as described in this Privacy Policy, our Services do not respond to "Do Not Track" requests or other similar mechanisms.

## OPTING-OUT, REMOVING, OR MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION

We offer several ways for you to update your information that is obtained and stored by PacSun, including options to change your account preferences, remove your email from e-mail updates, and others.

  * To modify your account information, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section.
  * To unsubscribe from electronic updates, please visit your Contact Preference Center, where you can manage your subscriptions so you only get what you're interested in.
  * You may also [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus).

Please note that due to email production schedules, you may receive emails that are already in production. We may also maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

## CONTACT US 

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://www.pacsun.com/contactus).
